You can now run your entire Shopify store directly inside of Claude
using Shopify's official AI toolkit.
This was released by the president of Shopify,
Harley Finkelstein, just a week ago.
And it's kind of a big deal.
This allows you to use the toolkit to connect right into Claude
and all of its AI capabilities.
And unless you've been living under a rock for the last few months,
Claude is a whole AI ecosystem.
It's not just a chatbot. It can think for you,
it can create things for you,
and it can even do tasks for you.
So if you plug those things together,
it can run your entire Shopify store.
And that's exactly what I've done.
So in this video,
I'm gonna show you the simplest and easiest way to set up Claude
and the Shopify AI toolkit.
And I'm gonna give you three use cases that you can be using right now
to grow your store. Let's go.